{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1170,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":13,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si9850","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_2","title":"If you feel that your current accountant is holding you back, it might be time for a change.  Take two minutes to complete our 8-question quiz and see how well your current accountant scores... ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si9986","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10000","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide5182","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Button_2","si9986","si10000"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5182"}}},{"id":"si10593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_4","title":"Please tell us your name... ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10564","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10580","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_1","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Slide10592","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Button_4","si10564","si10580","Text_Entry_Box_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10592"}}},{"id":"si10670","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10660q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10781","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10777","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10704","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"How long do you spend on admin and paperwork each month? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10719","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A full day or two ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10719_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A full day or two\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10730","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10734","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Several hours ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10730_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Several hours\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11168","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11172","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Hardly any time at all. I just snap my receipts using my smartphone and technology does the rest! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11168_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hardly any time at all. I just snap my receipts using my smartphone and technology does the rest!\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si10785","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide10660q0","for":"Slide10660q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10799","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide10660q0","for":"Slide10660q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10660q0","for":"Slide10660q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10660","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10704","si10723","si10734","si11172","si10785","si10799","si10813"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10660"},"question":{"interactionId":"10684","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"How long do you spend on admin and paperwork each month?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["3"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"“The days of typing expenses and other data into a spreadsheets are gone. Spend your time doing something you enjoy instead.” ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11316","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11316"}}},{"id":"si11505","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11504q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11434","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","roles":{}},{"id":"si11371","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","roles":{}},{"id":"si11383","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"How often do you meet with your accountant to discuss how your business is doing? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_4","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11398","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"At least once every quarter ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11394_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"At least once every quarter\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si11406","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11410","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"At least once every year ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11406_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"At least once every year\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11421","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"We only ever meet to talk about our accounts, tax returns or their fees ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11417_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{"answer":{"title":"We only ever meet to talk about our accounts, tax returns or their fees\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_1","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide11504q1","for":"Slide11504q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11480","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_3","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide11504q1","for":"Slide11504q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11494","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11504q1","for":"Slide11504q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11504","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si11383","si11398","si11410","si11421","si11466","si11480","si11494"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11504"},"question":{"interactionId":"11363","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"How often do you meet with your accountant to discuss how your business is doing?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"“In our experience, meeting at least once per quarter is essential if you want to get maximum value from the relationship.” ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11536","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_11"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11536"}}},{"id":"si11697","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11696q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11626","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","roles":{}},{"id":"si11563","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_12","roles":{}},{"id":"si11575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","title":"Does your accountant take an interest in your personal and family goals, as well as your business goals? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11587","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11591","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_15","title":"Yes, all three! :) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11587_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_7","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, all three! :)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si11598","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_16","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11602","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"We only talk about business goals :| ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11598_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_8","roles":{"answer":{"title":"We only talk about business goals :|\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11609","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11613","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"We don't talk about goals, full stop :( ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11609_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_9","roles":{"answer":{"title":"We don't talk about goals, full stop :(\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11658","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide11696q2","for":"Slide11696q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11672","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide11696q2","for":"Slide11696q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11686","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11696q2","for":"Slide11696q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11696","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si11575","si11591","si11602","si11613","si11658","si11672","si11686"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11696"},"question":{"interactionId":"11555","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Does your accountant take an interest in your personal and family goals, as well as your business goals?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"“We believe that the main reason for running your own business should be to give you and your family the lifestyle you want. That's why we put personal goals first, then work with you to create a business that delivers them.” ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11728","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_21"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11728"}}},{"id":"si12081","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12080q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12010","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","roles":{}},{"id":"si11947","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","roles":{}},{"id":"si11959","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"Does your business have an annual forecast? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11971","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11975","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"Yes! We review and update it regularly ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11971_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_13","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes! We review and update it regularly\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si11982","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11986","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"Yes, but it's a bit out of date ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11982_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_14","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes, but it's a bit out of date\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11997","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"We don't have a forecast ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11993_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"We don't have a forecast\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12042","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12080q3","for":"Slide12080q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12080q3","for":"Slide12080q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12080q3","for":"Slide12080q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12080","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si11959","si11975","si11986","si11997","si12042","si12056","si12070"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12080"},"question":{"interactionId":"11939","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Does your business have an annual forecast?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"“We believe that running a business without a forecast is like driving a car without being able to see out of the windscreen. You might get to where you're intending to go, but you'll get there quicker and with less stress if you can see the road ahead of you, and have the route planned out.” ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11920","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11920"}}},{"id":"si11889","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide11888q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11818","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","roles":{}},{"id":"si11755","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","roles":{}},{"id":"si11767","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"Is your accountant using the latest tech? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11779","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11783","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Yeah, they're all over that shit! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11779_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_10","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yeah, they're all over that shit!\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si11790","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"They still use a lot of spreadsheets and pieces of paper ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11790_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_11","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They still use a lot of spreadsheets and pieces of paper\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11801","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"They use calculators, fountain pens, and probably an abacus ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11801_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_12","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They use calculators, fountain pens, and probably an abacus\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11850","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide11888q4","for":"Slide11888q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11864","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide11888q4","for":"Slide11888q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11878","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide11888q4","for":"Slide11888q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide11888","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si11767","si11783","si11794","si11805","si11850","si11864","si11878"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11888"},"question":{"interactionId":"11747","quizId":377,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"Is your accountant using the latest tech?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"“The world is changing, fast. We believe that embracing new technology can make everyone's lives a lot easier, freeing up your time and energy to focus on doing what you love - and growing your business.” ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12112","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_41"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12112"}}},{"id":"si10071","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"Time for a change? It's your call... ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_2","roles":{}},{"id":"si12133","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12141","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10137","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10141","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10155","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12129","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Your accountant scored ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12137","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"out of ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10061","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10061"}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Accountant Test","class":"project","title":"Accountant Test","children":["Slide5182","Slide10592","Slide10660","Slide11316","Slide11504","Slide11536","Slide11696","Slide11728","Slide12080","Slide11920","Slide11888","Slide12112","Slide10061"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide10660q0","Slide11504q1","Slide11696q2","Slide12080q3","Slide11888q4"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":5,"passScore":4}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5182","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide10592","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide10660","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide11316","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide11504","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide11536","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide11696","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide11728","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide12080","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide11920","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide11888","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide12112","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide10061","title":"Slide 13"}]}